divisare.com 2015-06-09

# Privacy - Divisare by Europaconcorsi

## Divisare protects your Privacy

Your privacy is a top priority for Divisare, and we make every effort to protect it. Divisare respects the online privacy of its users, in accordance with Italian law 196/2003.We will never sell or rent out your personal information to anyone, and it will never be used for any purpose other than to communicate with you and send you information about Divisare. Absolutely no Spam. That’s a promise.

## The information we collect 

There are basically two pieces of personal information that need to be provided in order to use Divisare:

  1. Your name and surname
  2. Your e-mail address

Your e-mail address will never be disclosed or made visible to others

## Why we collect your personal information

One of the main goals of Divisare is to encourage the spreading of ideas and communication among design engineers. In order to facilitate these exchanges, we have created a place where people – those who wish to do so – can talk about themselves and provide, on top of the personal data referred to above, additional information about who they are and their architectural tastes (for example, favourite architects or works of architecture).

## How long we retain your data for

For as long as you want to. Remember that you can delete or edit your data at any time and with no need for intermediaries. Once you delete your data, it is destroyed forever. Divisare retains no data in off-line archives.

## Questions about privacy

Should you have any questions or concerns about the privacy protection policy of Divisare or about its data processing methods, please contact us at the following e-mail address: [support@divisare.com](mailto:support@divisare.com). We will get back to you within 7 days.

## Information Note on the Privacy

Pursuant to art. 13 of Italian Legislative Decree 196/2003, Code on the protection of personal data, we would like to inform you that following the consultation of this website, data pertaining to identified or identifiable people may be processed.

Your personal data will be processed at our company’s facilities by means of automated tools, for the time that is strictly necessary to achieve the purposes for which it was collected.

Specific security measures have been adopted to prevent the loss of data, unlawful or improper uses and unauthorized access. The sending of electronic mail to the addresses provided on this website entails the subsequent acquisition of the sender’s address, needed to reply to the requests, as well as any other personal data included in the message. Processing activities associated with the services rendered by this website are carried out only by personnel assigned to the processing.

The user is free to provide the personal data requested in the registration form in order to receive the services offered by Divisare. Providing incomplete or incorrect data may make it impossible for your requests to be met.

On the contrary, failure to fill in fields requiring optional data shall have no consequence on the provision of the requested service. The user is entitled to exercise the rights referred to in art. 7 of Italian Legislative Decree no. 196/2003 and, in particular, the right to access their personal data, to ask that they be rectified, updated and deleted, if incomplete, incorrect or collected in violation of the provisions of the law, as well as the right to object to the processing for legitimate reasons.

The Owner of the processing is Europaconcorsi S.r.l., with head office in Rome, at the address of Piazza Gentile da Fabriano 3, in the person of its legal representative pro-tempore, who users can contact by sending an e-mail to the following address: [support@divisare.com](mailto:support@divisare.com).
